<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Island of Hvar</string>
    <string name="description_text">
        Hvar is vaguely shaped like the profile of a holidaymaker reclining on a sun-lounger,
        which is altogether appropriate for the sunniest spot in the country (2724 sunny hours each year)
        and its most luxurious beach destination.\n\n
        Hvar Town offers swanky hotels, elegant restaurants and a general sense that, if you care about seeing and being seen,
        this is the place to be. Rubbing shoulders with the posh yachting are hundreds of young party goers,
        dancing on tables at the town\'s legendary beach bars. The northern coastal towns of Stari Grad and Jelsa
        are far more subdued and low-key.\n\n
        Hvar\'s interior hides abandoned ancient hamlets, craggy peaks, vineyards and the lavender fields that the island is famous for.
        This region is worth exploring on a day trip, as is the island\'s southern coast,
        which has some of Hvar most beautiful and isolated coves.\n
        The fabulous Hvar needs little introduction for anyone aware of the beautiful Croatian coastline.
        The sunniest island in Europe attracts thousands of boaters, party-goers, and nature lovers every year.
        It is an absolute must on anyone\'s Croatia itinerary. If you\'re only spending 24 hours in Hvar, make sure
        to follow this itinerary to get the best out of your Hvar experience.
    </string>
    <string name="enter_label">Enter</string>
    <string name="home_label">Home</string>
    <string name="tours_label">Tours</string>
    <string name="shop_label">Products</string>
    <string name="tours_header_label">TOURS</string>
    <string name="tours_content">Take a guided tour of the town of Hvar, swim in a secluded bay at one of the Pakleni Islands,
        and take dip off the shores of Brač Island on this catamaran cruise from Split. Enjoy a delicious lunch, snacks,
        and unlimited water, soft drinks, wine, and beer.
        Begin with a relaxed cruise on a mega catamaran to the beautiful Brač Island.\n
        Visit the town of Hvar, where a guide will take you sightseeing and show you the most important
        attractions of the old town.
    </string>
    <string name="shop_header_label">Domestic Olive Oil</string>
    <string name="shop_button_label">Continue Shopping</string>
    <string name="cart_content">Don’t forget about using the coupon codes you will
        find around our website. They change frequently, but are always a great bargain… if we
        do say so ourselves. If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out. We love
        helping our customers.
    </string>
    <string name="bottle_image">Image of the olive oil bottle</string>
    <string name="activities_image">Image of activities</string>
    <string name="product_size_label">%d ml bottle</string>
    <string name="activities_duration_label">%d hour duration</string>
    <string name="product_image_label">Bottle of olive oil</string>
    <string name="activities_length_label">%d hour</string>
    <string name="activities_image_label">Activities and Tours</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart_label">Add to Cart</string>
    <string name="activities_label">Activities</string>
    <string name="activities_header_label">ACTIVITIES</string>
    <string name="activities_content">Discovering Hvar Island, Croatia: A Mosaic of Experiences\nHvar Island beckons with a wealth of activities for all tastes. Explore Hvar Town\'s historical treasures, from the commanding Hvar Fortress to the vibrant St. Stephen\'s Square. Bask in the sun at pristine beaches like Dubovica and Milna, offering opportunities for water sports and relaxation.\nVenture to the Pakleni Islands for secluded paradises, while neighboring towns like Stari Grad reveal a different cultural hue. Indulge in wine tastings at local vineyards or savor the island\'s cultural essence at the Franciscan Monastery and fragrant lavender fields.\nHiking trails in the Hvar Nature Park offer breathtaking vistas, while the island\'s evenings come alive with vibrant nightlife in numerous bars and clubs. Delight in traditional Dalmatian cuisine and partake in seasonal events like Yacht Week and cultural festivities for a truly immersive experience.\nHvar Island\'s fusion of history, nature, and contemporary allure ensures a journey that caters to every visitor\'s penchant, crafting unforgettable memories in this Croatian gem.</string>
</resources>